const htmlData = [

    {
        "question": "Which tag is used to create a line break without spacing in HTML?",
        "options": ["<br>","<lb>","<break>","<newline>"],
        "answer": "<br>"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which tag is used to define a list item in an ordered list?",
        "options": ["<li>","<ul>","<ol>","<list>"],
        "answer": "<li>"
    },
    {
        "question": "How can you create a hyperlink that opens in a new tab?",
        "options": ["target=blank","target=_blank","target=new","target=_new"],
        "answer": "target=_blank"
    },
    
    {
        "question": "Which tag is used to define a heading in HTML?",
        "options": ["<h1> to <h6>","<heading>","<head>","<head>"],
        "answer": "<h1> to <h6>"
    },
    
    {
        "question": "Which tagis for a text input field in HTML?",
        "options": ["<input type","<input>","<input type=text>","<text>"],
        "answer": "input type=text>"
    },
    
    {
        "question": "How do you create a radio button in HTML?",
        "options": ["<input>","<radio>","<input type=radio>","<option>"],
        "answer": "<input type=radio>"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which HTML tag is used to create a hyperlink?",
        "options": ["<a>","<link>","<href>","<url>"],
        "answer": "<a>"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which HTML tag is used to create an image on a webpage?",
        "options": ["<img>","<picture>","<image>","<src>"],
        "answer": "<img>"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which HTML tag is used to create a paragraph of text?",
        "options": ["<<paragraph>>","<p>","<text>","<para>"],
        "answer": "<p>"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which HTML tag is used to define a table row?",
        "options": ["<td>","<table>","<tr>","<row>"],
        "answer": "<tr>"
    },
    
]

export {htmlData}